Hello.
こんにちは
It's white.
白 いですね
This is often said.
よく言われます
That's right.
そうだ よね
Are you taking care of yourself in some way?
なんかケアしたりしてるのかな?
ERROR
特にしてなくて、 もともと白いのかな?
That's what I think.
って思ってます
I'm grateful to my parents.
親に感謝ですね
I wonder if it's been a while since I talked to a man like this?
なんかさ、 こうやって今男の人と話すのは 久しぶりなのかな?
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
ERROR
じゃあさ、 ちょっと 緊張してるかな?
I think you're a little nervous.
ちょっと 緊張してると思うんですよ
Why don't you just talk to me?
なんで、 僕とちょっとお話ししません?
About 15 hours.
15時間くらい
No.
ないわ
Maybe about 5 minutes?
5分くらいかな?
Is it okay if I talk to you for about 5 minutes?
5分くらいでちょっとお話ししてもらってもいいかな?
I wonder if you have a part-time job or something?
なんかさ、 バイトとかってさ、 何かしてたりするのかな?
Currently, I am working part-time at a coffee shop in Harajuku.
今は、 原宿の喫茶店で バイトをしてます
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
There is such a cute child.
こんな可愛い子 いるんですね
I'm here.
います
I said it.
言っちゃいましたね
You're cute, smile.
可愛いね、笑顔ね
Hey, if she's this cute, she'll be popular.
ね、こんだけ可愛かったらさ、 人気の的でしょう
It's a cafe.
カフェね
There are a lot of cute girls at the cafe.
いっぱい可愛い子がいます、カフェ
Are you serious?
マジですか?
Like Yoridori Midori?
よりどりみどりみたいな?
More green.
よりどりみどり
Are you serious?
マジですか?
Tell me about that coffee shop.
その喫茶店ちょっと教えて、俺に
A coffee shop?
喫茶店?
Because I want to know the place.
場所知りたいからさ
It can be your address or your finger number.
住所でもいいし、指番号でもいいよ
Actually, I run a coffee shop.
実は、 喫茶店やってるんですけど、
I also have a different job, Oh, that's right.
違う仕事もしてて、 あ、そうなんだ
Can I come out for a moment, me?
ちょっと出てもいいですか、僕?
I have pale skin, so I'm wondering if this is a tofu shop?
なんか肌白いんで、 お豆腐屋さん?
Ah, not at all.
あ、全然違います
That's right.
そうですよね
You're such a cute girl, you don't live in the downtown area.
こんな可愛い子ね、 下町にはいないよね
I'd like to give you a little hint.
なんか、 ちょっとヒントっていうか、
What are you doing?
何してるんですか?
I also dance.
踊ったりしてます
Are you dancing?
踊ってるんですか?
Baudry?
ボードリー?
It's not Beaudry.
ボードリーじゃないです
I'm dancing.
踊ったりしてるんだ
Dance like that.
そう踊る
dancer?
ダンサー?
I'm not a dancer.
ダンサーじゃないです
Isn't there such a cute dancer?
こんな可愛いダンサーいないか
Hey, could you please tell me something?
ちょっとじゃあ、 教えてもらってもいいかな
I'll keep it a secret between just the two of us.
2人だけの秘密にするんで
Do you want to block the microphone?
マイクとか塞ぎますか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
I'm an underground idol.
地下アイドルをやってます
Are you serious?
マジですか?
I see.
なるほどね
That's why it's so cute.
だからこんな可愛いんだね
surely.
確かに
It's a little different, after all.
ちょっと違いますもんね、やっぱり
If you can do that, you'll certainly no longer see anything like that.
そうやれれば、確かにもう それしか見えないですよ
Well, after all, idols...
ね、やっぱさ、 アイドルの方ってさ、
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
To be honest, I also have something I'd like to ask you.
ぶっちゃけ、僕もさ、 聞いてみたいことあるからさ、
May I ask?
聞いてもいいかな
Is there any bullying?
いじめとかあったりするの?
Won't it become like a power struggle?
勢力争いみたいになったりするんじゃないの?
It's a group of girls, so that's true, right?
女の子の集団だから、 あるはあるんじゃないですか?
Are there any groups you belong to now?
今、所属してるグループはない?
There isn't.
はないです
Then, in the dressing room, things like that happen.
じゃあちょっと楽屋とかで、 そういう感じあったりするんだ
But there are some things that are a little confusing.
でもなんか、ちょっと揉めるとかはありますね
Why do you get into so much trouble?
どういうことで結構揉めるの?
The parts of the song, my phrases, etc.
歌のところとか、 私のフレーズとか、
I wonder if that's what it's going to be like.
そういうところになるのかな
I'm having trouble with that part as well.
そういう部分でも揉めますね
I'm not in the PV for a while, right?
ちょっとPV私の方が出てないっしょ、
Like.
みたいな
Isn't it a little less than 10 seconds?
ちょっと10秒少なくない?
Is there something like that?
みたいな感じとか、 あったりするの?
Please keep that in mind here.
それはもう、ここで、 心に留めて
That's right.
やっぱそうなんだ
Well, I guess that's true.
まあちょっと、やっぱそうだよね
We do things like handshake events together.
握手会とかもさ、 一緒にするわけだよね
It's something that I look up to, like an idol group.
なんかさ、憧れのさ、 アイドルグループとか、
I wonder if there will be one?
いたりするのかな?
I like Nogizaka.
乃木坂さんが好きです
Nogizaka?
乃木坂?
I see.
なるほどね
It sure looks like it already.
確かにもう、いそう
Looks like it's good.
いそうですね
Who is this?
なんか誰よ?
Do you have a favorite group?
好きなグループの人はいるの?
I'd like to use this as a reference.I admire people like this.
ちょっと参考にしたいなとかさ、 こういう人に憧れ持ってるんだ
Is there such a thing?
とか、 あったりするの?
I have already graduated, but I loved Maian.
もう卒業しちゃったんですけど、 マイアンが好きでした
Shiyashi Maian.
しやしマイアン
It's cute, isn't it?
かわいいよね
I think it's cute and beautiful.
かわいいときれいかな
Yeah.
うん
But isn't the system quite different?
でも、系統結構違くない?
That person is pretty.
あの人きれい系じゃん
surely.
確かに
different.
違う
If anything, I feel like Naa-chan.
どっちかって言うと、なあちゃんみたいな感じだよね
I see.
なるほどね
After all, what kind of system is there, and what is good about it?
やっぱそこの、 どういう系が、どういうところがいい?
Do you like it?
好きかな?
After all, I can stay at the center forever.
やっぱり、 ずっとセンターでいれる、
I feel like it's popular.
人気の感じとか
But in the center, yes.
でもセンターにいる、 そうですね
Certainly.
確かにね
Let's sing a little influence?
ちょっとインフルエンスで歌っちゃいます?
I want to sing.
歌っちゃいたい
I see.
なるほど ね
Can I ask you about it a little later?
ちょっと後で聞かせてもらおうかな
It's a little embarrassing right now.
今ちょっと恥ずかしいよね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's like Maian.
とか、マイアンみたいな感じなんですね
But it's something like that.
でもなんかあれっすね
Now, is it the center?
今じゃあ、 センターなの?
I'm not the center right now.
今はセンターじゃないです
It was the front center, but the front was
前センターだったけど、 前 は、
A little bit.
ちょこっと
Well, I just fell off.
じゃあちょっと今落ちちゃったんだ
It's a bit of a shock.
ちょっとショックだね
There are a lot of things.
いろいろやっぱあるんだね
Somehow, I'm taking this as an opportunity.
なんかさ、これを機になんかさ、
Taking this opportunity, I would like to say something like this.
これ を機にさ、 なんかちょっとこう、
I'm thinking about calling it a new one.
新規ってにしようかなみたいな、 考えたりしてるの
I agree.
そうですね
recently.
最近
Yes, yes.
はい はい
So, I'm going to ask you some questions about your hardships.
で、辛労相談みたいな、ちょっと聞きますよ
People say I look exactly like Yasshi Akimoto,
僕、 秋元やっしーそっくりと言われてるんで、
It's a bit similar, isn't it?
ちょっと似てますよね
Are they similar?
似てるのかな?
You're so kind.
優しいね
Of course I feel like I'm producing it,
もちろんプロデュースする感じなんで、
Well then, I'd like to ask you something.
じゃあちょっと僕、 なんか話聞きますよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Well, well, I was an underground idol,
まあ、 まあ、 その 地下アイドルをやってて、
Have you been scouted recently and carry it around with you?
最近スカウトされて、 ほうほう持ち歩いてて?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Well, I guess it will.
まあ、されるだろうね
surely.
確かに
And it's Harajuku.
しかも原宿だもんね
that's right.
そうです
But it wasn't scouting for underground idols or anything.
でもそれ地下アイドルとかのスカウトじゃなくて、
Female announcer?
女子アナ?
Ah, I see.
ああ、なるほどね
I was scouted by someone, and I was very happy.
の スカウトをされて、 ほ うほうほう
I'm thinking of doing that, but
それをやろうとも思うんですけど、
I also want to go to a women's college.
女子大にも行きたくて
I see.
なるほど
Well, I don't know if I should stop watching that idol or not.
まあ、自分ではもう、 そのアイドルの方を やめるのかやめない
I don't know why, but I went to a women's college,
の かちょっと分かんないけど、 ちょっと女子大に行って、
It's like, ``Idols are really tough when it comes to love.''
みたいな感じの、 やっぱアイドルって恋愛とか厳しいんだもん
hey.
ね
Is love prohibited?
恋 愛禁止なのかな?
TRUE?
本当?
Just a little bit, after all, it's there,
ちょっとね、 や っぱあるわけだから、
Maybe it's because I want to be liberated,
そういうのに解放されたいってのもあるのかもしれないけど、
It looks like a female announcer, it looks like a female announcer.
女子アナっぽいっちゃ女子アナっぽいよね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Wouldn't it be better if we just went with two people?
二頭流で行っちゃったらいいんじゃないですか?
Female announcers and women's universities.
女子アナと女子大
surely.
確かに
Pitcher and catcher, I just play them.
ピッチャーとキャッチャーね、やっちゃうくらいだから
I feel like I'm doing it as a two-way student, even though I'm going to a women's college.
二頭流でやっちゃう感じでさ、 女子大行きながらさ、
Wouldn't it be nice to make an announcement?
アナウンスもさ、 しちゃえばいいんじゃない?
surely.
確かに
I think that's the way it should be.
そこはさ、 そういう感じにしちゃえばいいと思うんだよね
I'm also interested in the romance business.
僕、恋愛事業も気になってるんですけど、
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいるの?
I'm not there right now.
今いないです
Really?
本当に?
But I'm sure you can't say that.
でも確かにね、 いえないよね
I'm sure there aren't any.
確かにいないだろうけど
Well then, what if I quit being an idol?
じゃあ さ、 アイドルやめちゃったりとかしたら、
Do you really want to go on a date?
や っぱデートしたいの?
I would like to.
したいですね
Where would you like to go on a date?
どれどこデートしたいの?
I want to go out normally.
普通にお出かけをしたいです
I see.
なるほどね
Like shopping.
ショッピングとか
Right now, I'm thinking about a lot of things, and I'm thinking about things while walking.
今ちょっとね、いろいろ考えて、 考えて歩いたりすることもや
Yes, there is.
っぱ あるんですね
Please go on a date with me then.
その時僕とデートしてくださいね
You're so kind.
優しいね
I have become a handshake god.
握手神になっちゃったけど
Did that relieve your tension?
そしたらね、 緊張はほぐれたかな?
I felt relaxed.
ほぐれました
Get ready.
準備します
It makes me feel safe.
安心になってくるんで
Can I stop the camera?
カメラ止めてもいいかな?
I'm still nervous, I guess.
まだ緊張してるね、やっぱりね
I have a way to relieve tension, so can I use it for a while?
緊 張を解ける方法があるんで、 ちょっとかけちゃってもいい?
Then close your eyes.
じゃあ目つぶってて
What's your favorite type?
好きなタイプは?
Kind and
優しくて、
He's a very clean person.
すごい 清潔感がある人ね
I mean, it's refreshing.
爽やか系ってことね
Then open your eyes.
じゃあ目を開けてみて
Because the eyes are enchanted.
目魔法かかってるから
It looks refreshing, right?
爽やか系に見えてるでしょ
You definitely don't have it.
絶対持ってないでしょ
After all, it's a bit of a lie.
やっぱりね、ちょっと嘘つくのはね
Are you not good at it?
ちょっと苦手かな?
Head, can I get used to it?
頭さ、慣れてもいい?
頭?
It's about as good as your head, right?
頭くらいいいでしょ?
Because my hair has dirt on it.
髪ゴミついてるからさ
Just take out the trash.
ゴミ取るだけだから
I can't really get rid of the trash.
なかなかゴミ取れないね
It's in this area.
この辺に入ってる
How about having your ear touched?
耳触られるんだ、どう?
The one that tickled me.
くすぐったやつ
It's cute.
かわいいね
Don’t like tickling?
くすぐり苦手?
So instead of tickling me, can I push you down?
じゃあくすぐらない代わりに、 押し倒していい?
It's really cute.
ほんとかわいいね
It's the center.
センターだもんね
So, do you want me to touch the inside of the center as well?
じゃあ僕もセンター内に触っていきですか?
But I touched it.
触っちゃったんだけどさ
Quite...
なかなか...
This is just counting the nose pattern.
これね、鼻柄数えてるだけだから
Oh, now?
あ、今?
You think I'm touching your boobs, right?
おっぱい触ってるって思ってるでしょ?
Not that, this...
そうじゃなくて、これは...
I'm counting the nose stalks.
鼻柄数えてるの
1、2、3、4...
Is there a lot of fashion like this?
こういうファッション多いのかな?
There may be many.
多いかもしれない
Like One Piece?
ワンピースみたいな?
It suits you, after all.
似合うね、やっぱり
I see.
なるほど
I wonder if there are many pale colors like this in dresses?
ワンピースとか、こういう淡い系の色が多いのかな?
many.
多い
Don't you hate it when your boobs break?
おっぱいも割れたりするの嫌いじゃないの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
real?
ほんと?
I'm not shy at all, but hey, hey, hey.
全然恥ずかしがってないけど、ほらほらほらほら
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look, look, look.
ほらほらほらほら
Maybe it's a little weak for me?
ちょっと私に弱めなのかな?
Can I do something more embarrassing?
もっと恥ずかしいことをしてもいいかな?
yes.
はい
Well then, idol...
じゃあ、でもさ、 アイドル...
After all, there's always something that could happen.
やっぱり、いつ何時もさ、 何かあるかもしれないじゃない
Is it?
ですか
Maybe fans will come suddenly.
も しかしたらね、 ファンがパッとやってくるかもしれないじゃ
yeah.
ん
Hoi!
ほ い!
Something like that.
みたいな感じで
Hey, my knees, below my knees, this is something...
ちょっと、膝、膝下、 これ、なんかさ、
the...
その...
Can I look down to below the knees?
膝下ぐらいまで 見てもいいかな?
So far, so far.
ここまで、ここまで
What if that's all?
ここまでだったらどう?
Normally, you show your shoulders, right?
普通にね、肩を見せるでしょ?
When I show off these shorts.
このショーパンとか見せるとき
I just wanted to see some shorts.
ちょっとショーパンぐらい見たくて
Can I take a look?
ちょっと見てもいい?
Your skin is so beautiful.
めっちゃ肌きれいだね
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
But are you really conscious of not getting burnt?
でもこれやっぱ焼けないように やっぱり意識してるの?
I am doing.
してます
That's right.
そうだよね
Otherwise it wouldn't be this beautiful.
そうじゃないとこんなきれいにならないよね
Ah, wonderful.
あ、素晴らしい
I highly recommend this, seriously.
これ すすめだね、マジで
Don't you hate it when your feet are touched?
足さ、触られたりするのがさ、 嫌いじゃないかな?
get nervous.
緊張する
It's not like it's ticklish.
こう、くすぐったい感じではないんだ
tickles.
くすぐったい
Does this kind of feeling tickle?
こういう感じがくすぐったいの?
How does it feel to be touched like this?
こうやって触られるのどう?
this?
これ?
Characters like this.
こういう字や
Your skin is really beautiful.
め っちゃ肌きれいだね
You can touch it all the time.
ずっと触ってられるよ
I just want to check the lining.
裏地確認したいだけだから
lining?
裏地?
Lining, lining.
裏地、裏地
Lining?
裏地を?
How far is the silk connected?
シルクどこまで繋がってるの?
The lining is black.
裏地黒なんだね
lining?
裏地?
This one has a black lining.
裏地黒だよね、これ
Is this the lining?
これが裏地?
this?
この?
different.
違う
What is it?
何かな?
I tend to wear bold colors like black.
結構黒とか大胆な色着るんだね
What other colors do you wear?
他にはどういう色着たりするの?
I also wear white, light blue, and pastel colors.
白も着るし、 水色とかパステル系も着る
Pastel?
パステル系?
Does it look like yellow?
黄色とかって感じかな?
I don't wear yellow.
黄色は着ない
Light blue or something.
水色とか
Light type?
淡い系?
Pastel colors?
パステルカラー?
It looks good on you.
似合いそうだね
If you touch the pastel here,
ここのパステル触ったらさ、
Really?
本当 に?
Can I touch the pastel for just 30 seconds?
パステル30秒だけ触っていい?
10 seconds, 10 seconds.
10秒、10秒
10 seconds?
10秒?
Can I count 10 seconds?
俺数える10秒でいい?
I'm counting.
数えてるのよ
In your brain.
脳内で
Because I couldn't feel it.
感じ取れなかったから
Well then, it becomes a bit of a punishment game.
じゃあちょっとね、 それだとちょっと 罰ゲームになります
Can I touch your breasts?
おっぱい触っていい?
5 seconds,
5秒、
5 seconds.
5秒
It smells really nice.
め っちゃいい匂いですよね
I can feel my breasts.
おっぱいはさ、感じたりするの
Shall we make a peace?
ピースしちゃう?
together.
一緒に
If you just point at the camera, idols are what they are, after all.
とりあえずカメラ向けたらね、 アイドルってやっぱね、
We're going to dance.
踊っちゃうじゃん
Shall we dance together?
一緒に踊っちゃう?
Like this.
こうやって
Let's dance.
踊っちゃう
I'm in trouble.
困っちゃってる
So let's make peace together.
じゃあピースしようか、一緒に
It's cute, really.
可愛いね、本当に
When I dance, I sit like this for a long time,
踊るときってさ、 こんな感じでずっと座って、
Well, until it's time for a quick dance,
まあ、さっと踊るときまでだろうけど、
Basically it stands.
基本立つでしょ
Could you please stand up for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらっていいかな
I feel a little relieved,
僕ちょっと安心ってばれてるんで、
There are two of us, so we have to do a synth.
二人いるシンサーしなきゃいけないんですよ
You can stand up.
立 ってもらってもいい
kana.
かな
All of a sudden, I'm embarrassed,
いき なりやっぱ恥ずかしいからさ、
How about showing this side of this skirt?
このスカートこら辺まで見せちゃうってのはどう?
You saw it just now.
さっき見えたじゃん
My timing is fine.
自分のタイミング大丈夫だよ
That's sexy.
セクシーだね
And then, it was a little bit the other way around.
そしたらさ、 もう逆にちょっとさ、
Because I have to cover my head and hide my ass.
頭隠して尻隠させないとなっちゃってるから
So please listen to my request,
じゃあ僕のお願いをちょっと聞いてもらって、
As for the underwear, I wonder if I'll show you this part at least.
下着のところさ、 この辺だけでも見せたりしないかな
Only the top?
上だけ?
Only on top.
上だけ
Rock, paper, scissors.
じゃんけんするじゃんけん
I'll give you a par, par.
パー出すよ、パー
I'm really going to make a par.
本当にパー出すよ
I'll go then.
じゃあいくよ
Only if I lose.
負けたらだよ
At first it was like rock, paper, scissors!
最初はじゃんけんぽい!
The reason I lost was because there was no subject.
負けたらだったのは主語なかったからな
You lost, right?
負けたよね
Well then, just a little.
じゃあ ちょっとね
I'll take my clothes off, I'll take my clothes off, I'll take my clothes off.
俺脱ぐよ、俺脱ぐわ、俺脱ぐわ
Shall we take our clothes off together at the fair?
フェアで一緒に脱ごうか
I could have just been in my underwear.
下着姿だけでもいったらさ
I like the style.
スタイルいいな
Maybe you're not careful.
気をつけてないかもしれない
This is a punishment game.
これは罰ゲームですね
So, can I have you look aside during the punishment game?
じゃあ罰ゲームで 脇見してもらっていいですか?
side?
脇?
side.
脇
You usually wear something sleeveless on your armpits, right?
脇ってやつ普通にノースリーブとか着るでしょ?
Mr. Zaba.
ザバさん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Eh, like this?
え、こうやって?
It's cute, kind of.
可愛いね、なんか
It's really good.
めっちゃいいじゃん
Is this what I'm warping?
これがさ、自分でさ、 反ってるの?
Well, let's take it off.
これともさ、脱ごうって
I'm warping myself.
自分で反ってる
What, are you warping yourself?
え、自分で反ってるんだ?
Yeah.
うん
So, is your hair naturally thin?
じゃあもともと毛薄いのかな?
Yeah.
うん
That's right.
そうだよね
It tickled.
くすぐった
Ah, yes, it's quite like that.
あ、そう、結構あれなんだ
It doesn't tickle me, so I guess it's okay.
くすぐらないから、ちょっといいかな
Do this at the bottom too.
下もこうやって
I never tickle you.
絶対くすぐらないから俺
It doesn't tickle me.
くすぐらないよ
I have to tickle.
くすぐりはしなきゃいけない
It smells really nice.
めっちゃいい匂いするね
Because the dentist doesn't have it.
歯医者にないからね
Can I have a little bath to cool off?
ちょっと浴び冷えとしてもらっていい?
Around here?
この辺?
I'm really hungry.
めっちゃお腹空いてる
tickles.
くすぐったい
Like this.
こうやって
Finally?
やっとく?
Yeah.
うん
Come with me for a moment.
ちょっと一緒に
Look, I have hair too.
見て、俺毛もいってるから
Yeah.
うん
Can I take off my tickler?
くすぐらを脱がしてもいいかな?
Yeah.
うん
Can I take it off?
脱がしてもいい?
Open your butt.
お尻開けて
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
So, can I ask you to do something more embarrassing?
じゃあ俺もっと恥ずかしいことをお願いしてもいいですか?
It's embarrassing, I guess.
恥ずかしいんだ、やっぱり
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
So, have you ever seen your own mango?
じゃあさ、自分のマンゴーとか見たことある?
do not have.
ない
It's quite interesting.
結構興味津々だね
I can feel it quite a bit.
結構感じるよね
touch.
触る
So how about I touch it with my feet?
じゃあ足で触っちゃう?
first.
最初
Yeah.
うん
Shall I touch it with my foot?
足で触っちゃおうか
Wouldn't it be nice if it were legs?
足だったらいいでしょ?
Will I get angry?
怒られちゃうかな?
Pinch it with your other foot and touch it a little.
反対の足でも挟んで、ちょっと触って
Become the tip.
先端になる
Because I'm looking closely.
近見ってるから
That's amazing.
すごいね
You're so kind.
優しいすごいね
I'll say it.
言っちゃうんだ
It's cute.
可愛いね
It's like this.
こういう感じ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Thickness.
太さ
A microphone is something you can eat with your mouth.
マイクってさ、口で食えるものじゃん
picture?
え?
Is that so?
そうだっけ?
This mic is a little scattered.
このマイクさ、ちょっと散る
From the other side and.
向こうからそして
change?
変える?
That's no good.
ダメだろ
Is it okay to say 0.0?
0.0って言っちゃダメ?
After all, you shouldn't say it.
言っちゃダメやっぱり
No?
ダメ?
No.
ダメ